Hell has frozen over.
Snowmageddon is a adventure, science fiction, tv
movie film directed by Sheldon Wilson.
An Alaskan town is in danger of destruction by a mystical snow globe that appears on a family's doorstep, wrapped like a Christmas
gift, and causes deadly "natural" disasters in their own town, while simultaneously occurring in the snow globe.
John Miller, played by David Cubitt.
Beth Miller, played by Laura Harris.
Rudy Miller, played by Dylan Matzke.
Jennifer Miller, played by Magda Apanowicz.
Derrick Reed, played by Jeffrey Ballard.
Larry, played by Lorne Cardinal.
Leah Diane Gibson is a Canadian actress.
The tone is thought_provoking.